<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Nokia | Parul Midha's Weblog]]></title>
  <link href="http://parulmidha.github.io/blog/categories/nokia/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://parulmidha.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-06-21T15:12:26+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://parulmidha.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Geek's Corner]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nokia, Microsoft Working Even Closer, Collaborative Effort Coming Soon]]></title>
    <link href="http://parulmidha.github.io/blog/2013/06/12/nokia/"/>
    <updated>2013-06-12T11:29:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://parulmidha.github.io/blog/2013/06/12/nokia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> <img src="http://i0.wp.com/igyaan.in/wp-content/uploads/2013/06/ttg-aithangtrongthoathuanmicrosoftnokia-1-1.jpg" alt="nokia microsoft" /></p>

<p>During a Lumia 925 briefing in the UK, Nokia revealed that they’ve tightened its ever-growing bond with Redmond-based Microsoft, makers of the Windows 8 (mobile and desktop) platform. Nokia UK’s Ray Haddow stated that the Finnish company has been “working even closer” with Microsoft and we can expect to see new collaborative efforts in the near future. Engadget reports that Nokia and Microsoft will work to raise Nokia’s profile.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p></p>

<p>Nokia and Microsoft first entered into a “broad strategic partnership” that made Windows Phone OS its “primary smartphone strategy,” but there have been rumours of Nokia coming to market with a tablet for years now.</p>

<p>The company went on to discuss marketing opportunities it’s seizing upon as a result of its Microsoft affiliation, so we very well might just be talking about plans for a new promotional blitz. What was less clear is if all that might be focused on a particular product (and we certainly expect the EOS to be a big win for both Nokia and Microsoft) or if it could be more broadly Lumia- or WP-focused in general.</p>

<p>Could this mean that Nokia might be ready to enter the Windows-powered tablet space? No telling what these two have in store but we should know in the next few weeks.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
